Cinderella's Sister
Beg.gar.
Episode 4
Get lost.
Get lost! I said leave!
You beggar-like thing, you ugly thing!
You horrible, beggar-like thing!
This is my house. Get lost right now!
Will you not get lost right now?! You beggar!
Will you not get lost right this moment?
I don't want to.
What?
You get lost.
What did you say?
I don't like being here either, but
if you tell me to get lost I'll never leave.
-This little-
-I really am sick of being here, but I'll leave on my own accord.
Just because someone like you tells me to get lost I won't do so.
Hey, Song Eun Joo! Stop right there!
Hey!
I like you, Song Eun-jo. I want to go out with you. Let's go out. I'll be good to you. Kim Dong-Soo
These little punks won't study like I tell them to...
Their writing is just... goodness.
What is this?
Hey, Song Eun Jo!
Unni, I'm sick of this!
You... this little!
Let go of me!
- Hey, let go of this!
- Let go!
- Stop that!
No.
Is this what you wanted? I can do this.
I'll dislike you. I'll hate you!
I'll bother you so much that you will want to die!
You think I can't do that?
Unni, you're bleeding! Oh dear.
Oh my god.
You horrible bitch!
Hey, stop right there!
You asked me to date you. Let's date!
Hyo Seon is back!
Why are you crying? What is this?
Grandma!
Oh my goodness, what happened?
What happened?
I'm hanging up. If you call my house again, I'll kill you.
You know I always do what I say I will, right? If I say I'll bite you, I really will bite you!
Hyo Seon!
-Hyo Seon, why are you crying?
- Mom!
What happened? Why are you like this?
-Mom!
- Oh my child.
You know my heart hurts when you cry. Don't cry
Mom, oh my gosh. Eun Jo is really a bad girl.
Why did you give birth to her? You should've have.
That's what I'm saying. I wish I hadn't been born.
What are you saying?
You come here, you little brat.
Why do you always only reprimand me?
Will you not come here?
I don't want to!
Honey, Hyo Seon is in shock. Why are you shouting?
-You come here.
-Dad! Ah, Mom! Mom!
-Honey don't be like this.
-Come here!
Follow me!
Dad, I was wrong! I was ...
Shut your mouth! Come here.
Dad, I was wrong!
What did you do this time that Hyo Seon is like that?
Stop it.
You do your work, and you, follow me.
Goodness, this little wretch. Why do you cause such a fuss trying to do something about that little girl?
I would've already stewed ten of those things, if I were you.
Why? You said your heart hurts? You said your heart hurts because your child is crying?
Go out right now! He said to follow him.
You're really going to use all of this?
Until the relationship between you two improves,
I won't allow Eun Jo to use a separate room.
If it keeps going on like it is right now, you two will lock yourselves up in your separate rooms and
it seems that you won't even talk to each other. If it becomes like that,
you will slowly abandon your relationship.
And it seems I will regret making a family like this.
My heart hurts, you brats!
Won't you give me the cane?
Why? Do you want to get hit too?
Sir, can I just try to talk them out of it?
Then, you get hit too. Stand over there.
Hyo Seon, come here.
Dad...
Come!
If you did something wrong, then say so.
Dad, I did wrong.
I won't do it again, please forgive me.
Did you do wrong?
I did wrong.
Go.
Eun Jo, come stand here.
If you did something wrong too, then say so.
Dad.
Did you not do something wrong?
Dad, she did wrong.
Boss.
♫ You wouldn't know ♫
♫ How much I loved you! ♫
I'm putting the phone down.
♫ As time goes by ♫
♫  You will regret it ♫
♫  With burning tears overflowing my eyes ♫
He's sleeping now.
Why don't you try to change your number? I'm hanging up now.
Oh, please go quickly! He's hitting someone.
I don't know whether she'll die before tonight's over.
Hurry, hurry.
Honey...
Dad.
Hyo Seon, Hyo Seon? Hyo Seon!
Wake up, Hyo Seon!
You...
what kind of kid...
Goodness...
Is your head full of rocks? Why are you so stubborn?
You could've just said you did wrong! Why did you...
Let's see where you got hit.
Turn around and sit down.
Okay.
If you were a kid who listened to what I said, you wouldn't have got hit by the boss.
If you were someone who listened to what I said,
you wouldn't have been able to hold your tears in like that with glass embedded in your knees.
I'll bring some medication, but whether you use it or not,
Whether you die starving or getting hit, do whatever you want.
That's how it sounds like when the wine is being fermented.
Don't get hit.
If you're getting hit, run away. You're an athlete at running away.
If you act this stubborn one more time, you'll really be dead to me then.
Eun Jo,
please give me a reply.
Okay.
It hurts, right?
Yeah.
My calves don't hurt at all.
Even if I bleed, it doesn't hurt.
I don't even know why.
My heart just flies into the sky.
It seems like it would even go until the moon.
Her fever is down, Honey.
Honey.
Go to Eun Jo.
Hey, hey! Part-timer!
Get up.
Well, here the madame is saying she's gonna go to some temple.
Will you escort her? My brother told me to go,
but I... How could-
Okay, I'll go.
Where did he go?
It's definitely not because I don't want to go.
There's something called perspective and relationships, right?
Ah, I forgot again.
Kids and adults are all the same, telling an adult like me to do this and that.
Since a while ago she kept saying to call you.
Go here and there, do this and that - I just can't even keep u-
Did you call for me?
Are your calves okay?
If you wear long pants, won't it brush against your pants?
Who was the girl who was messing around with you by the lake yesterday?
What?
It's embarrassing to have to keep asking you the same question, do instead of replying "What? What?", give me a response.
I'm asking who the girl that was messing around with you by the lake yesterday was?
What is it? Why are you laughing?
You came here at the crack of dawn to ask me that?
Could you not sleep a wink the entire night because you were so curious? Is that so?
That's why the only one who's at a loss here is my late sister.
She married Dae Seong who had nothing, and just struggled, struggled and struggled.
And then as soon as things were starting to look up, she fell ill.
Then she just. Left the world! Goodness...
I can only go somewhere if I have somewhere to go.
This is all all my father's fault.
He had sold off all the property he had.
I can only take it and do this or that with it if there was something left for me to take.
Go here or go there.
Come in.
I'm embarrassed too, so don't make me repeat myself.
You'll have to work a bit.
Kyung Wha Chung playing Tchaikovsky: Violin Concerto In D, Op. 35
This is the debut album of
Korean violinist, Kyung Wha Chung. It's my favorite album.
Did you know how old Kyung Wha Chung was when she recorded her first Tchaikovsky piece?
Oh those. Those are my second favorite albums.
That's my favorite-
That's the catalog of my favorite artist, Song Sang Gi. Song Sang Gi's life was...
Hey, if someone's talking, then listen.
- Who was that woman?
- Who else would it be?
She's my friend's younger sister, who kept my things for me when I moved out of the dorm.
My friend is in the military right now and not here, so his sister came instead. Why?
Then that's fine.
Hey!
Will you really date that kid Dong Soo?
That little punk is messing around with me!
Pretend like our relationship is good.
If you pretend our relationships good in front of Mom and Dad for a few days,
he'll give his permission for you to move into your own room.
If someone's talking to you, reply a bit!
Understood. I'll do that.
I'll be back.
- Have you eaten breakfast?
- Yes, I ate a bit.
You should eat breakfast before you go.
I'll eat it at the temple.
Eat well.
Let's eat.
Unni, I'm sorry.
I did wrong.
No, I did wrong.
- Have you come?
- Yes.
- Hello!
- Okay.
Hey, why are you here?
She said she would go on the train herself.
I told her I would take her to the temple, but she kept refusing.
Is that so? Okay, understood. Do your work.
Hello! Yes, yes.
I called you because of the blessings prayer. Yes.
Please look after us well this time too.
Huh? I mean, I could only write something if I had the talent.
If you only write the way you've been doing, I will read it well.
Please give it to my new wife when she returns.
What? She didn't go?
Ah, I don't know either.
I don't know either...
Bueno, piano. That's right.
Why don't we try again? Let's keep working hard.
My student is making so much progress. I have to study a lot more in advance.
Animal.
[I am a student studying Spanish. And you? I am also
a student studying Spanish. She is the secretary at the university. ]
Hey, part-timer. A customer came. But, who is he?
Your immature sibling. Did you "chew some gum" in your youth?
( Were you part of a gang?)
Where are we going?
To you, red, blue and yellow,
I'm going to give you three bottles with these colors in it. Whenever you get placed in a tight spot,
you break each of these by throwing it on the ground. And from these broken bottles, smoke comes
pouring out. That'll save your life.
I definitely remember going with Father to the house where you and your mom lived.
And also I definitely remember taking out that fairy tale book out of your bookshelf and reading it.
Yeah! The sweet potatoes your mom had baked then were really good too.
- What are you talking about?
- Hey, I'm talking about me as Hong Gi Tae.
What are we to do if I become the owner of that theme park?
The children should be called to experience all that's in the fairytales.
Isnt it wicked?
Is it not?
But why did you and my mom always tell me you would kill me whenever I say this.
I can create a theme park that's much better than Disneyland.
Art
A flower that does not wither.
Father and daughter
Why are you so bad?
Teacher, my condition is really bad today.
Can I not go home?
What about the recital? What are you going to do about the recital?
Teacher..
It's a bit late. Why are you out here?
What happened? You didn't answer your phone all day.
There was something I had to do.
Where did you go?
I went to go finish it off, Honey.
There is already a lot of work to do, so I'm not sure if I can have student Gi Hoon to take me anywhere every time.
I felt sorry to you, so I took a train there.
I'm sorry, I lied.
Honey, I am not trying to blame you. Don't get me wrong.
Looking at Eun Jo's calves
the reddness festering
in case you might've felt bad, that's why I was going to go to the temple.
But if the calves were like that, she definitely would've been surprised.
If I leave her as is, the child ends up hurting somewhere else.
In case, she might fall sick, I went to the traditional clinic that I used to get medicine from when she was young.
The traditional clinic had moved and wasn't there.
I went around trying to find out where they had moved.
I'm sorry.
No, no.
In case you were to do this, that's why I was going to go to a temple.
But, I'm not good at lying...
I'm sorry. I'm really sorry.
No, no.
I'm sorry.
Hey, if you come out of there alive,
it'll be because I told you about the red bottle and the blue bottle...
So you'd better be good to me.
There will be no problem, legally.
I already drew up the document, so read it over and sign it.
Memorandum of renunciation of inheritance.
What are you doing?
Alright, I didn't think you were going to stamp this without any conditions.
What's your condition?
There must be something you're thinking of, what's your condition?
Will you give me half of Hongjuga Corporation?
Let's hurry up and finish this. You must have seen the security standing by as you were coming in,
so you'll have an idea of what will happen if you cause a ruckus.
I will add another zero to the sum you're thinking
so save your time in holding out.
Half of Hongjuga Corporation?
Your mom would have given birth to you with that kind of mindset,
but a young guy like you doen't even drop a single drop of sweat.
Don't ever mention my mother with that mouth of yours, Madam.
Is your mom a queen that I can't even mention her name?
- If it were not for your mom,
- Don't mention my mother with your mouth!!
Are you somewhere you dare to raise your voice?
You're a lawyer, right?
Note down whatever I say from this point.
If you need to prepare a meeting like this again, next time
why don't you give me a chance to have my lawyer present as well.
Additionally, I have no intention to sign a renunciation of inheritance memorandum like this.
If by any chance, you're thinking of using force against me,
Either cut off nerves so much that movement isn't possible
Or you'd better kill me.
Crawling out of here alive in a pitiful state
I am the type to go straight to a news outlet or a newspaper company.
You don't think I'd do it? I will do it. Ten times or more than a hundred times.
Mom was treated like a bar hostess
and her son was treated like trash. Where is there for me to fall lower?
-Are you threatening me now?
Think whatever you want.
Are you confident you can kill me?
How can I help you?
What do you want me to do to help you?
Blue Lord of the East...
Red Lord of the South...
White Lord of the West...
Yellow Lord of the Center...
Imoh Year (2002) April 8th, Owner Gu Dae Seong
respectfully asks the territorial gods (5 direction gods)
that I shall be making several hundreds, thousands of batches of leavening.
The path is pressed vertically and horizontally forming a border
and each of the five gods is arranged on the periphery.
We bow as we offer up this wine.
Let there be no vermin present and do not let any trace of useless spirits linger.
When drunk let upstanding men be both awake yet drunk.
To small men, let them become humbled and quiet.
I humbly request this multiple times.
My words are not falsehoods nor fabrications
so Gods please listen. From the otherworld bring blessings
and let not our human desires not be any different now and forevermore.
Congratulations.
Song Eun Jo has won first place in the math contest in the school.
She will participate in the National Math Competition next month.
- You did a good job.
- You really did well.
You did well, right?
It's okay, it's alright. You can just win first place next time, our baby.
Oh, I'm so proud of you, my daughter!
Okay?
I'm really usually good at pointes in ballet.
I'm really really good.
Okay, you did well.
Wow, she's so good!
Good job!
I'm actually... so good at this,
that I used to get complimented by my teacher every day.
I do it like this...
It doesn't matter,
- I just wanted to be complimented by just one warm-hearted person.
-You came?
What you were pointing to, was it here? I didn't know where you were, so I was looking ev-
Certificate of Achievement
You did well.
You really did well.
You did so, so great, Eun Jo!
Aigoo, you're so smart.
Eun Jo!
I'll give you a present. Follow me.
You saw right? This is how you unravel it,
It's a very old item, it might be more older than you..
I kept it well ... at first it was too valuable to give to you
that my hands shook, but with this
you can write a letter, a diary..
Whenever you hold it in your hands, think of me..
So unenthused.
How could you do this? Why didn't you give it to me?
I went out to the ballet competition, but why aren't you giving one to me? Why are you only giving one to her?
Oppa, did you forget? Don't you know who you belong to?
Eun Jo.
Did you sleep well? It's Sunday, why don't you sleep a little longer?
There's some wine that hasn't fermented properly.
The farthest to the right, the second jar from the back,
it's totally ruined.
You figured that out? Did you? How?
It isn't making any sound.
Okay. I'll go check it.
Hyo Seon is home.
Did Gi Hoon leave well?
He left well.
What are you saying?
- About what?
- Where did he go?
- Who?
- You said he left!
I don't know, who?!
Unni... I love him.
Oppa Gi Hoon went into the army.
Because I never called that person...
Because I never described that person to someone else...
I don't know what to call him.
That person is that person. If that person isn't that person,
then who does he become?
Does this make sense?
Hyo Seon.
Can you give this to Eun Jo for me?
Hello.
Let's smile!
Dear Eun Jo, I'm leaving because I don't think I could go if I saw your serious face.
I'm going alone now, but later on I'll take you to Ushuaia, to the moon and to the stars.
Don't run away. Don't go anywhere and just wait for me at home, I won't let you leave.
Hiking Specialty Store
Will you hold onto me?
♫Again today my memory led me astray♫
Though your knees bleed profusely, unable to cry. You Hong Gi Hoon-like fool. (Hong Gi Hoon played a fool in the 90s on television)
if you hold onto me, I think I could stop right here.
♫where you can't hold me again ♫
Before I get on this train, please grab me,
Eun Jo.
♫ Saying I want to see you and hold you again ♫
♫While looking at heaven I'm praying ♫
♫ It must be you ♫
♫ I cannot be without you ♫
♫ Like this for another day, month or year ♫
♫I don't mind even if I am hurt ♫
♫ I don't mind even if my heart breaks ♫
♫because, yes, you are the only one I love. ♫
Because I never called that person by anything, I...
Eun Jo.
Just like a cuckoo bird cries cuckoo, cuckoo.
Just like the Ibis cries out its own call...
Eun Jo.
Just like a bird, I called my own name and cried.
♫ Like this for another day, month or year ♫
♫I don't mind even if I am hurt ♫
♫ I don't mind even if my heart breaks ♫
♫because, yes, you are the only one I love. ♫
8 years later
8 years later,
We at Daeseong True Family, in response
will globalize makgeolli
So that makgeolli is not just a trend, but becomes recognized as a mainstream liquor
It is time to take proactive and significant action
Our Daeseong True Family uses environmentally sustainable 100% Korean rice
will add value to the traditional liquor market. Additionally increasing its prestige
so that it can be enjoyed in all corners of the world. We will put efforts to make the best alcohol in the world.
We will give all of our best efforts.
Thank you.
I hope we work together in the future.
- Good work.
- Yes, thank you.
- I hope we work together in the future.
Ah, can a factory inspection be possible?
Of course.
Then, once our planning team has set a date in our schedule, we will contact you.
No. Instead of contacting us, just drop by anytime.
Are you that confident?
Of course.
Son Sang Gi Exhibition
Instead of that one, Oppa Gi Hoon said he liked this painting the best.
That it reminds him of his mother who passed away in the hospital.
And so he would stare at this painting for ten minutes without looking away.
Why are you here?
I came to look at the paintings.
Did you come without knowing what this was, Unni? I came here knowing about the exhibit.
Did you not know? Oppa Gi Hoon told me.
That Son Sang Gi was exhibiting, so I should come by.
What did you say?
You don't know?
We're dating right now. Oppa Gi Hoon... and I.
♫ It must be you ♫
♫ I cannot be without you ♫
♫ Like this for another day, month or year ♫
♫I don't mind even if I am hurt ♫
♫ I don't mind even if my heart breaks ♫
♫because, yes, you are the only one I love. ♫
♫My bruised heart♫
♫ is shouting so that♫
♫ I can find you♫
♫ Wherever you are♫
♫ Can't you hear my voice?♫